https://williamtravisgroup.com/privacy-policy

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
Privacy PolicyJoseph2018-12-19T17:19:50-06:00
Who we are
The William Travis Group, Inc. (WTG) is a disaster recovery/business continuity consulting firm, located in Schaumburg, IL.  WTG has been in business since 1990; our website address is: https://williamtravisgroup.com
Summary
We do not collect any data that is not directly provided by you; comments are disabled globally and user registration is only open to WTG Employees.
What data we may collect and why
Contact forms
If you fill out a contact form, we may collect the data in the contact form.
This site is protected by reCAPTCHA and the Google Privacy Policy and Terms of Service apply.
Cookies
Generally, user registration is disabled and cookies are not used.
WTG Employees Only: If you have an account and login, a temporary cookie will be set to determine if your browser accepts cookies; this cookie contains no personal data. Other cookies will be set to save your login information and screen display choices. If you edit or publish an article, a cookie will be saved in your browser indicating the post ID of the article.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (ex. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the same way as if you have visited that website.
Other websites may collect data, use cookies, embed tracking or monitor your interaction with the embedded content.
WTG Employees Only: If you have an account and are using Gravatar, a hash may be provided to Automattic Inc.; the Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/
Who we share data with
We do not share any collected data with any external entities.  We may share the data you provide in a contact form with the relevant Internal Employee at WTG.
How long we retain data
WTG Employees Only: We store the information provide in a Registered User’s Profile; users and website administrators can see, edit or delete this information at any time (except username). Login cookies last for two days and are removed if you logout; if you select “Remember Me”, login cookies will persist for two weeks.  Screen options cookies last for a year, article cookies expire after 1 day and temporary cookies are discarded when you close your browser.
What rights you have over your data
WTG Employees Only: If you have an account on this site you can request to receive an exported data file; you can also request that we erase any data stored. This does not include data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal or security purposes.
Toggle Sliding Bar Area
Design
Executive IBPD
Iterative Business Process Decomposition (IBPD)™
Critical Application Workshop
Recovery Architecture Design
Systems Availability Architecture Design
Data Availability Architecture Design
